magecomp.com 2019-10-06

# Privacy Policy

Attention! Magento is Officially Ending Support for 1.x. after June 2020. Hurry before Sunset. [Migrate Now](https://magecomp.com/magento-2-migration-service.html)

### Privacy Statement

At MageComp, we believe in keeping users privacy and collect data in the safest way as possible by complying to GDPR rules. This policy summarizes what personally identifiable information we may collect, and how we might use this information. This policy also describes other important topics relating to your privacy. In this whole policy "we", "us" and our refers to **MageComp Inc.**

### Information Collection

We will only collect personally identifiable information (such as name, title, company name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) that you voluntarily provide through our website or e-mail correspondence. We also collect general information (such as the type of browser you use, the files you request, and the IP and country from which you request information) to improve our website and better meet your needs. All of your personal information including credit card information and the ordering process is handled through our 256-bit data encryption Secure Socket Layer (SSL) connection.

### **About cookies**

A cookie is a small file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.

These cookies will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date unless deleted by the user before the expiry date or a session on the other hand when the web browser is closed.

Cookies do not typically contain any information but stores some personal information about you. On our site, we use cookies for the following purposes...

1\. authentication - we use cookies to identify you when you visit our website and as you navigate our website.

2\. status - we use cookies to help us to determine if you are logged into our website.

3\. personalization - we use cookies to store information about your preferences and to personalize the website for you.

4\. security - we use cookies as an element of the security measures used to protect user accounts, including preventing fraudulent use of login credentials and to protect our website and services generally.

5\. analysis - we use cookies [to help us to analyze the use and performance of our website and services.

6\. cookie consent - we use cookies to store your preferences in relation to the use of cookies more generally.

### **Cookies used by our service providers**

Our service providers use cookies and those cookies may be stored on your computer when you visit our website.

We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Also, we are using IP Anonymization in Analytics and We have turned off Data sharing that allows us to customize what data we want to share with Google and what data we want to keep with us as part of security.. Google's privacy policy is available at [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

We use Sendinblue, Wigzo, Google AdWords & remarketing, Tawk.to Live Chat and Freshdesk Ticket System to serve a personalized store experience and quickly get in touch with our customers. This service may uses cookies for their purpose to provide better service which you can view the privacy policy of this service provider at their respective website.

To learn how to manage cookie on your computer: **[read this guide](https://magecomp.com/manage-cookies)**.

### **Right to erasure**

Any individual can request for their data to be removed or deleted when there is no compelling reason for a business to continue processing that information. To remove your personal information from our website and data you can **[make a request here](https://magecomp.com/support/).**

### Use of Information

Before we collect any personally identifiable information, we will provide you with an explanation of any possible uses of your data. The information you supply will be used by us to send you any requested information of the products and services, fulfill your orders and respond to your inquiries. We may also use the information to inform you about new features, products or services if you explicitly instructed us to do so.

### Other Important Information

This website may contain links to other sites. We do not endorse or accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. Additionally, some of our Web pages may contain "cookies," - data that may be sent to your Web browser and stored on your computer. This allows our server to "recognize" you when you visit our Web site in the future. Most Web browsers can be configured to not accept cookies or to notify you if a cookie is sent to you.

If you have questions about the way MageComp is handling your User Personal Information, please let us know immediately. We want to help. You may contact us by filling the contact form. You may also email us directly at support@magecomp.com with the subject line "Privacy Concerns." We will respond promptly within 7 days.

It may be necessary, if required by law or judicial or governmental investigations, to release your personal information.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. We will promptly reflect any such modifications in the Web page.
